[Music]
hey guys good afternoon and welcome to
your stocks I'm pavitra and we have a
lot of queries to get to but before that
a quick look at the markets which has
been holding up very well today uh even
right now we're seeing 100 Point gain on
the index slightly below that 19800 Mark
but it's been a pretty steady session
for the markets uh the banks have come
off a little bit in the past few minutes
that's definitely something to keep an
eye on right now the Nifty bank is
trading with gains of just just around 2
T of a percent so you can see that
there's been a sharp slide in the Nifty
Bank we're at the day's low as well over
there what's holding up well today are
some of the stocks from the broader
Market specifically the small cap stock
so that index is holding up well midcaps
also pretty much in step with what's
happening on the index but there has
been a little bit of a cooling off there
as well Advanced decline still very
positive it's over 2 is to one but you
know earlier in the day we were at 4 is
to one so there's definitely a little
bit of cooling off that we've seen in
the mid and small caps space let's get
to all of our queries then and first of
all let me invite Our Guest on the show
we have rajad BOS joining us as well as
Shina Madam to answer all of your
questions rajat is going to be looking
at the technical side and shahina will
of course give us her fundamental
perspective as well rajat Shah as always
thank you for you know joining us in the
show and taking out the time for all of
these queries that have come through the
first query is someone who holds 100
shares of sign which were bought at 1345
he also has 50 shares of indent bank
which he bought at 19 uh around 1190 now
he says he's a long-term investor he
wants to know whether he should hold
this uh stock both signed as well as
indent bank or whether he should sell
and sort of get out of these names maybe
look at something else as well um
shahina coming to you first on S take us
through what you expect you know he
bought at 1345 the stock is currently
over 1,700 so some money has been made
and this stock has seen a very good run
this year as well do you think there's
more to go and we also have the the
earning season starting so ahead of that
how would you position
yourself I think scient is one of the uh
you know still attractively valued
despite the run up in the uh in the
smaller in the midcap companies for it
so I think you know even at current
levels he can continue to hold
especially also that sent has more than
66% equity in the demerged uh company
that is recently listed so to that
extent there is value there also
continue to hold I think the numbers for
all it companies are likely to be
subdued for the quarter so I don't think
SCI will be any very different but at
the same time I believe that you know
this current one to two quarters will be
the bottoming out so it looks good for
the overall sector and science
especially in the sector as far as
indent goes I think it has been like uh
you know if you take a very long term it
has not been a performer but in the
recent past I think the management is
getting its act together and we've seen
a bit of performance in the last couple
of months I believe that at current
valuations of 1.7 times book and also
the refocus uh you know on improving the
margins on the nyss I think one can
continue to hold even indent Bank you
can hold it with a stop
loss okay got that so that is the call
on both sent and indic rajit coming to
you and once again let me start with
sent with you as well this stock is in a
huge run up right if you look at it for
the year it's up over 100% how are the
charts looking right now do you expect
that this kind of good momentum will
continue There is a possibility that
good momentum might actually continue
but then uh uh I would say that you
would do I mean the investor would do
better to actually B part profits if it
were to fall below
1560 and uh it should have a final stop
loss around say 1,400 but otherwise I'm
definitely in agreement with sa that
one can continue to hold uh despite the
fact that it has actually been posting
alltime
highs uh few weeks back but still it has
not really Fallen below the 9we moving
average so the uptrend is quite intact
so the closest stop loss is uh say 1560
and the farthest stop loss will be
around 1,400 I would also give a hold
regarding indas in bank I what I would
say is that if I were in the Investor's
shoes initially I would look at levels
of around say 1,400 or say about uh
1390 kind of levels for my stop loss and
if that stop loss gets hit then I would
uh like to exit the position at least
partly and by any chance you should not
be continuing to hold the stock if it
were to fall below 1350 another thing I
would like to say the bank as a sector
is actually pretty much weak it is going
in tandem with the midcap index as well
as the nifty 50 but the bank Nifty has
the least of
strength uh rajat I'm glad you actually
mentioned that what are the kinds of
levels that you're working with on the
Nifty bank because you know we were
discussing this on one of our earlier
shows as well that it's not been very
consistent right you have one up day one
down day for the Nifty Bank even today
right now there's been um a near 270
Point drop from the top what are some
near-term levels that we can work with
near term levels pitra it will be uh say
44300 then
44,000 uh that would be the this range
that 44300 to about
44,000 this will be the first support
area but if it were to fall below say
44300 and also c z below that then uh
you should be expecting the recent low
to be retested
and one stock keep an eye on that that
is HDFC bank if it were to fall below
1500 this stock is the weakest among the
large Bank stocks and it can go down to
test 1400 levels so HDFC bank is a big
uh I mean it has real big uh weightage
in the bank Nifty so Bank nifty's
performance is to that extent f by that
if you look at kotak bank that's also
Distributing so I'm not very bullish on
Bank as such as a
sick okay and believe me we've all been
keeping an eye on HDFC bank and seeing
what's happening over there but Raja
thanks for taking us through those
levels the next query that comes through
is from Mega shasa she writes to us from
up now she says she has 100 shares of
all cargo Logistics which she bought at
50 so she's made a lot of money on this
one she's a medium-term investor uh
maybe from these levels not willing to
hold for too much longer and wants to
know whether she should hold or book up
profits shahen with this kind of a runup
you know the stock is currently over 265
she obviously got in at a very good
price do you think that this is one
where you should get out because um in
the recent pass the stock has not been
doing very
well she should hold with a very strict
stop-loss you know close to the current
price she's making good money so that is
why I would just recommend she can
continue to hold because you see the
last quarter numbers were very good and
also uh you know I think they have been
raising funds through one of the
companies that is again recently listed
their real estate Wing So to that extent
I think you know the balance sheet is
also pretty strong at the same time I
think you know keep an eye on the
stop-loss because you have lot of issues
happening in the Middle East as you've
been covering also and that could affect
some of the
business okay so strict stop loss and
can hold for now uh rajat what is your
thought on all cargo logis ICS I mean at
the highs I think the stock was over 47
480 kind of levels as well so it's not
done well in the recent past but of
course she's sitting on good profits
what would you recommend to such an
investor look if you look at the weekly
chart if you look at the monthly chart
then you will see the distribution uh
signs are clearly visible but yet I
would say that uh because we are seeing
bounces happening so book part profits
but keep a close stop of about 220 if if
see on any week it is actually closing
below 220 get out of the stock Lock
Stock and
B okay got that that is on all cargo
Logistics another query coming in this
is from Risha Agarwal who writes in from
New Delhi she holds 20 shares of bharti
Airtel but she bought at 250 so well
that stock is over 950 right now and she
is asking whether to stay invested or
switch to some other Telco well there's
not too much in terms of what you can do
within the Telecom space but Shina do
you think bharti AEL is a good space to
remain invested considering that she's
already made good
money yeah I would think so because now
it's become more of a doolly if you're
looking at shortterm pure trading then
yeah vone looks very interesting but I
personally wouldn't recommend at all
entry into vone I would stick with uh
you know one of the two one of the two
Telos that exist now and bti remains
like a decent bet to continue to hold
while I do believe that in the shorter
term it could consolidate because the
run up that we saw was on back of the
Improvement in arpus that they witnessed
so now I think that is not going to
happen in the near term and especially
with Reliance with Geo coming up you
know with the fiber uh the geofiber air
fiber so I think to that extent
competition is going to increase uh but
at the same time I think B is a decent
hold for the longer term so if a
long-term investor is holding continue
to hold okay continue to hold and she's
already made very good money on this one
uh rajat your thoughts on this and your
thoughts on vone idea and the kind of
move that we've seen in the stock of
course uh I'm not sure you would
recommend that but uh just your thoughts
in both of these
names well regarding B I would say
despite the fact that it is hitting
alltime highs uh if I'm not mistaken at
least
uh it is showing a lot of strength it
can continue how the investor can
continue to hold it
and I I would say that yes it is a du
poly more or less because Vodafone IDE
is not exactly a competitor of these two
uh the point is that I would rather I
would prefer a situation where these
duopoly becomes a Cooperative duopoly
just as we had a Cooperative oligopoly
in pins and that is of course getting
fractured at the moment but then uh in
this Cooperative duopoly is is a good
bet and one should continue what should
be the stop loss is if if the investor
is making real good money put a stop
loss below 900 on weekly closing price
basis and continue to write the movement
upward okay that is on bharti AEL the
next query comes in and this is
interesting Rupa aaral rising from
Kolkata she holds 255 shares of jubil in
Food Works which he bought at 693 so
seeing a bit of a loss over there the
stock is currently at around 530 like
you can see on your screen and she wants
to know whether to stay invested or book
her losses and get out of this one Shina
ahead of the World Cup do you think you
would stay invested in this one and how
much of an impact do you really uh
believe it can it can
ca I think the third quarter numbers I
mean going forward are expected to be
pretty strong so uh you know jubilant is
you know one of the leaders in his
product segments and will continue to do
well but but I think it is pretty
expensive and uh if you compare it with
valuations with uh uh with I think uh
some of the others in the segment like
for example Westlife I think there the
valuation also expensive but it's a
smaller stock midcap so I would prefer
so jublin is not my top pick in the
sector I would prefer one of the other
competitors for investment but if you're
holding it for the long term you've
gotten at a decent price which this
investor has not for my for from my
understanding but if you are holding it
for the very long term then yes I think
valuations will start coming and looking
attractive over a period of time but not
right away so I think it's a nice switch
to some other stock in the segment so
what would you like to switch to Shina
if you could advise her are you picking
Burgers
now W life yeah yeah all right got that
rajat coming to you as well what do you
think I mean she's gotten at a pretty
high level you know that's the problem
over here but how is this one looking on
the
charts
see it is one thing to buy this stock
between say 500 and 480 or 470 and if
one has actually got into this at a
higher level then at the moment unless
560 is decisively taken out which is
actually a strong Fibonacci resistance
area uh so if that is taken out then the
stock will move up but otherwise it will
consolidate but unless it falls
decisively below 52 20 I think she
should she or he should hold the counter
hold the
position okay hold for now that is on
jubilan food works with that it is time
for a short break but China Raj I
request you to stay on we have a whole
lot of more queries which have come
through and we want to get to all of
those but before that here's a quick
[Music]
break
welcome back you're still tuned in to
your stocks here on CNBC TV8 and we're
going through all of the queries that
you guys have sent in and answering them
with our experts we have rajat and
shahina to take us through their call on
these stocks and we actually have a
caller with us on the line Rona rajpal
is on the line from Hyderabad and he
wants to invest in Bea Foods uh ronak hi
thanks for you know calling in and tell
us why do you want to invest in Bea food
in
specific I have actually I'm a long-term
investor and I already have a port folio
of a few stocks but I'm looking to
invest in consumer goods or maybe fmcg
which I'm lacking in my portfolio so
since relatively older company and
recently listed so I'm looking to invest
in vectors and this is a long-term
investment I'm
guessing yes all rightest two Ls which
is being chaned over the next few weeks
all right let's ask our guest what they
think of this of Bea foods and whether
you should invest or not Shina your
thoughts thoughts on this one he wants
to invest around 2 lakhs in tranches
over the next few weeks uh wants to add
some kind of you know consumer uh names
to his portfolio and this is what he's
looking at would you suggest
it yeah it's a it's a good stock it's
got very strong Brands strong balance
sheet uh good growth also the only thing
that is negative about it is the
valuations it's extremely expensive you
know given the size it's much much more
expensive than its competitors like for
example even britania so to that extent
you know I would suggest buy it at dips
don't buy it right away buy it at
dips okay buy on dips for vectors rajat
your thoughts on this one it is trading
close to its all-time highs I think what
would you recommend and do you think
this kind of up move that we've seen in
the stock is likely to continue uh
essentially does it make sense for
someone to get in after this kind of run
up as
well see in 16 months it has quadrupled
from a low of uh
245 uh last year June to current price
of about 1,90 it is more than uh four
times I mean uh 300% appreciation has
already happened uh in this runup and
this is a parabolic run up if you look
at the weekly chart but definitely this
is uh the return return on Capital and
other uh things are pretty much good but
then I would say I completely agree with
sa that this is a good stock uh good
company great company maybe but it's not
a great stock at the moment given the
kind of valuation it is enjoying wait be
patient it will also come down because
there are technical indications that
over the period period of next six
months to one year you will get an
opportunity to buy it at least at a much
lower level say around 800 kind of
levels that would be that would give you
some margin of safety because at the end
of the day what you pay
is uh that that actually determines your
margin of safety however great this
company is if you pay too high a price
you will you will
suffer okay I guess China and rajat
absolutely you know agreeing with each
other on that ronak I hope that helps
you as well you know both of our guests
agreeing that you've done a great job
identifying this stock and it is a good
one to have in your portfolio but it is
very expensive it's run up 150% in just
this year so maybe if it comes down a
bit and you can get it on a slightly
lower level that would perhaps be uh
good for you in your portfolio but thank
you for calling in the next query comes
in from roh Jen who writes in from New
Delhi he holds 30 shares of SBI at 160
so he's made good money here he asks
whether to continue to hold or exit at
current levels rajat I'm going to come
to you because you said you're not very
positive on the banking space for
someone who's been holding from these
kinds of uh levels do you think uh you
would you know book B part profits or or
what advice would you give to someone
right now considering that you said
you're not too positive on the
banks not too positive on the banks for
several reasons I mean if you look at
the monthly chart of kak Bank you will
see uh negative divergences are
suggesting that people are actually some
people are actually exiting the stock
there if you look at State Bank of India
if you look at inves in bank if you look
at HDFC Bank State Bank is also
showing signs of distribution but State
Bank will become quite weak once it
falls below the support range between
520 and 480 once that level CES in there
would be there could be a Shar fall but
if I were in the shoes of the investor I
would have booked my profits
here okay Shina would you agree with
that advice or what would you recommend
on SBI because this is someone who's
clearly sitting on very good profits and
and you know has been invested for the
long term so I'm assuming they're
willing to stay in for a bit uh what
would you tell someone on
SBI well it is the best in its class of
PSU Banks so you can continue holding uh
credit growth is expected to be 13 14%
going forward and uh the focus of the
bank is now going to be on improving the
return on uh the weighted assets so I
think to that extent uh you know things
may look better going forward so one can
continue holding it's just about 1.7
times Price to
Book okay that is the call on SBI I'm
going to try to squeeze in one last
query before we have to B down we have
Kumar who writes to us from NOA he holds
100 shares of Hindustan copper which he
bought at 100 stock is currently at
around 155 he also has 300 shares of
sadbhav engineering which which he
bought at 10 Rupees that stock has
actually been seeing very severe Cuts he
wants to know the future prospects of
both of these Investments Shina your
thoughts on on Hindustan copper is there
anything else from the space that you
would you know like uh apart from this
also please go ahead with that and then
sbab engineering it's not a stock that
we talk about very often but he got in
at 10 the stock is currently at round
16 I think he can just book profits on
both he's you know making money and
while sbab is I in my view definitely
not a investment grade stock at best it
could be a trading stock loss making
very small cap micro cap so I would just
exit uh uh you know sbab engineering as
far as Hindustan copper goes I still you
know recommend a switch or a booking
profits you know government holds 66% of
the equity now if you see copper prices
have been coming down why to date they
are down still and uh you see the last
quarter numbers also were weak so in the
next couple of quarters I don't see too
much of a movement either ways uh so I
would just you know you know exit and
move on to some other stock or
sector okay God that rajat coming to you
as well on both of these names Hindustan
copper as well as SB engineering uh take
us through what you you know how do you
see these ones on the charts and what
would you recommend to someone who is
invested in
both see sadv engineering I would say
that now that it is hitting circuits on
the upside it would be better to take to
get out of it because there these kind
of stocks which gives circuit every day
for say eight session 10 sessions or
something when it comes down it will
also come down this way so you would not
get an exit then so exit sad engineering
regarding Hindustan copper I would agree
with sa for short to medium term but
those people who are planning to
accumulate Hindustan copper for the
longer term when I say longer term
actually I'm bullish for the longer term
on basic materials Metals minerals uh uh
over the next next five to seven
years there the technical chart suggests
that there is huge accumulation slow
huge accumulation has already happened
and slow accumulation is continuing in
it so if you have a real long-term point
of view then continue to hold on else I
would go with sa that book your profits
especially if it falls below
150 all right very helpful advice there
Shina rajat on that note we're going to
wind down but thank you as always for
joining us and helping us answer all of
these different queries that have come
in we're out of time on this edition of
your stocks but remember if you have any
queries you can always email uh them to
us and we will take them up with our
experts we're going to wind down for now
with the markets back above 19,800 stay
tuned closing bell is up next for the
final hour of trade
today
[Music]